// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Charminar is situated in which place?",
    answer: "Hyderabad",
    options: [
      "Jaipur",
      "Hampi",
      "Amritsar",
      "Hyderabad"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Victoria Memorial is situated in which place?",
    answer: "Kolkata",
    options: [
      "Bihar",
      "Kolkata",
      "Mount Abu",
      "Jodhpur"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Ajanta and Ellora Caves is situated in which state?",
    answer: "Maharashtra",
    options: [
      "Rajasthan",
      "Delhi",
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Maharashtra"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which Mughal emperor built Tajmahal at Agra?",
    answer: "Akbar",
    options: [
      "Jehangir",
      "Shahjahan",
      "Akbar",
      "Babar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Jagannath Temple is situated in which state?",
    answer: "Odisha",
    options: [
      "Delhi",
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Odisha",
      "Rajasthan"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Gateway of India is situated in which place?",
    answer: "Mumbai",
    options: [
      "Delhi",
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Mumbai",
      "Rajasthan"
    ]
  },  

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Mahabalipuram is situated in which state?",
    answer: "Tamil Nadu",
    options: [
      "Delhi",
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Odisha",
      "Rajasthan"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Qutub Minar is situated in which place?",
    answer: "Delhi",
    options: [
      "Delhi",
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Odisha",
      "Rajasthan"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Ajanta and Ellora Caves is situated in which state?",
    answer: "Maharashtra",
    options: [
      "Delhi",
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Maharashtra",
      "Rajasthan"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Konark Sun Temple is situated in which state?",
    answer: "Odisha",
    options: [
      "Delhi",
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Odisha",
      "Rajasthan"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];